https://www.goodwoodhardware.com/privacy-notice/

Information Collection and Use
Goodwoodhardware.com is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you elect to receive our newsletter or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items.
Registration
In order to process your orders placed on this website, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. This information is used to provide you with important Goodwoodhardware.com services such as automated order status updates via e-mail.
Order
Most of the information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order, wire transfer or check information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. See the Security section below for more details on security measures and procedures. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy.
Cookies
We customize certain Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our store but will be unable to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. The Goodwoodhardware.com shopping cart cannot function without cookies enabled so that the necessary information to process your order is retained. If you disable cookies, Goodwoodhardware.com will be unable to accept your online order. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party. We will, however, link data stored in cookies to the personally identifiable information you submitted while on our site. This allows us to personalize your shopping experience and discern user preferences to evoke subconscious feelings of familiarity and assurance.
Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Goodwoodhardware.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.
Sharing
We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.
FedEx Corporation
942 South Shady Grove Road
Memphis, TN 38120
1-800-GO-FEDEX
www.fedex.com
UPS Corporate Headquarters
55 Glenlake Parkway, NE
Atlanta , GA 30328
United States
We may frame or mask another web site so that the look, feel and interface simulate the experience of browsing a genuine Goodwoodhardware.com web page. Extreme care and discretion is exercised when evaluating third party sites. We only brand third party sites if their organization applies stringent security and privacy practices which parallel our own commitment to safe online shopping.
As our business continues to evolve, we may acquire or sell business units or subsidiaries. Customer information is one of the business assets that would be transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personally identifiable information would only be used in a manner consistent with our pre-existing Privacy Notice.
As our business continues to evolve, we may acquire or sell business units or subsidiaries. Customer information is one of the business assets that would be transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personally identifiable information would only be used in a manner consistent with our pre-existing Privacy Notice.
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
Children
Goodwoodhardware.com does not sell products for purchase by children. Youth-oriented products are sold for purchase by adults only. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use Goodwoodhardware.com in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 13. Goodwoodhardware.com is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Goodwoodhardware.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.
Security
Goodwoodhardware.com takes precautions to protect its customers’ information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software currently available in the industry – SSL. Goodwoodhardware.com uses the most advanced form of SSL software available: 128-bit encryption by VeriSign. To learn more about SSL, follow this link www.verisign.com.
Access to all of our users’ information is restricted. Goodwoodhardware.com operates in a secured and locked facility that requires all employees to check in and wear valid ID badges. Security cameras are positioned throughout the building in conjunction with multiple alarm systems. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. If you wish to have your financial information removed at the time of your order, you may opt to have your financial information deleted from our records upon completion of your order. Otherwise, you may contact us at webmaster@Goodwoodhardware.com. For future transactions, you will be required to re-enter your information.
Special Offers
Our special offers are sent only to customers who grant Goodwoodhardware.com permission to send them such information.
To honor the privacy of our users, we offer the option to not receive these types of communications. At the time of your order, you may opt to not receive special offers and news by clicking the appropriate field. Furthermore, all special offers are sent via e-mail and include an opt-out link if you no longer wish to receive special offers and news. Customers might still receive intermittent updates on products, services, specials or Goodwoodhardware.com news. Please reference the Choice/Opt-out section below for further details on how to be removed from our mailing list should you choose to be removed.
×
OK
Products
Collegiate
2019 National Championship
Apparel
Women
Women's Accessories
